http://www.newspaper-industry.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy:Bradley Culver ("Bradley") operates http://www.newspaper-industry.org and may operate other websites. It is Bradley Culver policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Bradley collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Bradley Culver purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Bradley Culver visitors use its website. From time to time, Bradley may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Bradley also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on http://www.newspaper-industry.org blogs/sites. Bradley only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Bradley Culver websites choose to interact with Bradley in ways that require Bradley to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Bradley gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up
at http://www.newspaper-industry.org to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Bradley are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Bradley collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Bradley. Bradley does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Bradley may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Bradley may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Bradley does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Bradley discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Bradley Culver behalf or to provide services available at Bradley Culver websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Bradley Culver websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Bradley will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Bradley discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Bradley believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Bradley, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Bradley website and have supplied your email address, Bradley may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Bradley and our products.
If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Bradley takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Bradley uses cookies to help Bradley identify and track visitors, their usage of Bradley website, and their website access preferences. Bradley visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Bradley Culver websites, with the drawback that certain features of Bradley Culver websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Bradley, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Bradley goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Bradley may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Bradley and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Bradley may change its Privacy from time to time, and in Bradley Culver sole discretion. Bradley encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy. If you have a http://www.newspaper-industry.org account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Recent Posts
The Newspaper Industry
Pages
Newspaper Ownership
Our Mission
Our Team
Privacy Policy
Say Hello
What Is a Newspaper?
